[theme music playing]
Don't bother coming back
until you have Arthur's body.
I'll pay you whatever you want
as long as you kill that bastard.
What I want to know
is who was behind this.
Do you think it's Diego?
That bastard.
You think I don't know what you did?
You had Arthur kidnap Ivy.
You can't stop our wedding.
I'll put a stop to all your plans.
-Let's go. We need to leave.
-Hon?
Let's go to Hong Kong.
We will get married there.
Let's start a new life somewhere.
Hon, relax.
If someone dares to try
to stop our wedding,
I won't let them.
Boss Jaguar says the Ardientes
are hot on our trail.
He also heard that Julio Ardiente
asked a private army to hunt us down.
But we won't let them intimidate us.
We'll continue with our casino operations.
[Jepoy] Now that I'm back,
I will make you suffer much worse
than I did back then.
I will use Jaguar's weapons
to wipe out the entire Ardiente clan!
We have been preparing for the forthcoming
Aguas-Ardiente royal wedding.
It is finally going to happen
a week from today.
-No! No! No! No!
-[pounding on table]
[Raul] Once we reach the casino,
go straight to the cashiers.
Get everything you can get.
Don't shoot unless necessary.
I want this to be a clean job.
Remember, we're going outside Ardiente.
It isn't our turf.
[Jepoy] They're tailing us.
Julio Ardiente's men.
It isn't safe to do this now.
[Julio] Ivy Aguas is not fooling us.
We are fooling her!
When we have sucked Ivy Aguas
bone-dry of her money,
and her good public image,
then she can be my present to you,
and you can do with her whatever you want.
[man] If you hadn't warned our boss,
we would've gotten into bigger trouble.
[Jepoy] Now that I have money and weapons,
I will stop your wedding
with bullets, Arnaldo.
And now, everyone,
-here he is!
-Hon?
As you can see, the man of the hour
-has arrived.
-[Ivy] Hon.
-You look beautiful.
-It's Mayor Arnaldo.
-Thank you.
-And of course,
we shouldn't forget about
Congressman Julio Ardiente!
He's also here, everyone.
-[Julio] Hello. Hello.
-[Phomella] Hello, sir. Hello.
-[chuckling]
-How are you?
This place looks like a bridal shop!
[chuckles]
[Julio] Look, don't get me wrong.
Uh, not that I'm complaining.
Hello, everyone!
Let me ask you a question.
Are you all excited
for the forthcoming wedding
of the century?
[all] Yes, Congressman!
That's nice to hear. Viva Ardiente.
[Arnaldo] Viva Ardiente.
You know,
the future of this family
has never been brighter.
And it can only get brighter
in the days to come!
[chuckles] Yes, Grandpa.
And it's all because of you.
No! Come on, Arnaldo.
Congressman…
Instead of "Congressman,"
may I call you "Grandpa" now?
Of course!
Grandpa, Arnaldo and I
would like to thank you
for giving us your blessing
to get married right away.
Well, if you put it that way.
You know, the truth of the matter is,
the first time I saw you two together,
I knew right away in my heart of hearts
that you were meant to be.
-Aww, hon.
-[chuckles]
[Phomella] Wow! Would you look at that?
It won't be long before Miss Ivy
becomes the new queen
of Poblacion Ardiente!
-[Julio chuckles]
-[Phomella] Oh, my.
We are all very excited.
And I'm sure you all feel the same.
-[Emilia] Hey, Phomella!
-[Phomella] Oh!
-Ms. Emilia, hello!
-[Emilia] Hi.
-It's nice
-How are you?
-to have you back here!
-Hello!
-It's been a long time!
-Hello.
Hi, dear friends! Hi!
You know, Phomella, my father
was so right when he said
that Ivy and Arnaldo
are destined to be together.
-[Julio] Yeah.
-Can you just imagine
their love story?
Ivy didn't even like Arnaldo
because, at that time,
Arnaldo was seeing Natalie.
-[laughing]
-[clears throat]
-Mama.
-Oh. I'm sorry.
That was so awkward. Sorry. [chuckles]
But you know, as they say,
if two people really love each other,
they will find each other in the end.
Look at you now! You're getting married.
Isn't that exciting, Auntie?
And, you know, I've prepared
something for both of you.
Um, to prove your love for each other,
I prepared a prenuptial agreement
that both of you will sign, of course.
[gloomy music playing]
Uh…
Mama, I think we should talk
about this in private.
[laughs] Come on, Arnaldo.
The public already saw the size
of my waistline earlier.
Besides, this is just to protect you.
-Come on.
-[forced chuckle]
Protect me from what? From Ivy?
Are you kidding me?
-[Emilia] Come on!
-[Julio] Come on, Arnaldo.
It's the millennium. The modern age.
It's normal to discuss these things.
Consider it. Won't your relationship
be stronger if you knew
that you were protected?
-[Emilia] Yeah.
-[Julio] I mean,
if the both of you are protected.
Mm-hmm.
Grandpa is right, hon.
With or without that prenuptial agreement,
my love for you will never change.
I love you so much!
-[Arnaldo] I love you too.
-[Emilia] Oh.
-That's really sweet.
-[applause on TV]
[Emilia] Oh, gosh.
Wait, Ivy.
Aren't you even going
to read the document?
Oh…
It says there that should you
and Arnaldo decide to separate,
one hundred percent of your assets
will go to Arnaldo.
[suspenseful music playing]
[woman] What?! All of it?!
One hundred percent?!
You are so greedy, Emilia!
[Jepoy] Don't sign it, Ivy.
[suspenseful music playing]
-Watch, Auntie.
-Hon, I love you so much.
I really do.
No amount of money can ever
compare to my love for you.
-[clears throat]
-That's why I will sign this.
Right now, while we're
in front of the camera.
This way, I can show Poblacion Ardiente,
Grandpa Julio, Mamita,
and Mama Emilia
just how much I love Arnaldo.
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[camera shutter clicks]
[suspenseful music playing]
Friends! As you can see, we are live!
The couple is signing a prenup agreement.
That's why I can really feel the love
and trust this family has for each other.
As you can see, Miss Ivy really
loves her soon-to-be family.
-[gloomy guitar music playing]
-[man] This is too much.
Auntie?
Diego, I promised Lily
that I would trust her plan.
But I can't allow those greedy
Ardientes to do this to her.
My goodness. Look at that.
[camera shutter clicks]
Miss Ivy signed it in front of you,
so you can see how much she truly loves
her soon-to-be family.
[suspenseful music playing]
[camera shutter clicks]
[Ivy] I know that prenup was a trap.
You thought I would say no?
You are talking to Ivy Aguas.
And the person who will beat me
at my own game hasn't been born yet.
[camera shutter clicks]
Diego, this is too dangerous.
Auntie, I understand you.
But the best way
we can help Lily right now
is by trusting her.
Auntie, your daughter
has been through so much.
She can take care of herself.
But for now, I will need your help.
We need to talk to all
the teachers here in Ardiente.
Let's convince them
to be steadfast and brave,
and to hold on to their principles.
We need to encourage them to be firm
in preparation for the upcoming elections,
so they won't be blinded
by the Ardientes' money,
or be threatened by their weapons.
Diego is right.
Our teachers are the key
to having an honest election.
If that's the case,
we shouldn't waste more time.
Let's start acting before
the Ardientes beat us to it.
Look, Papa. She signed it.
I know and it's got me thinking.
Hon, you think your mother's happy now?
She thought I would back out
because of the prenup.
Of course not, Ivy. I'm the happiest.
Because your union is a match
made in Ardiente's heaven.
Indeed! I agree a hundred percent.
Mm-hmm.
Well, well, well, my son, Arnaldo.
After a long and difficult hunt,
you finally landed Miss Aguas.
Did Arnaldo catch me, or…
was it Arnaldo who fell into my trap?
[suspenseful music playing]
[Julio chuckles] Well, you know, Ivy,
it really doesn't matter who got who
because, after the wedding,
you will become an Ardiente.
A bona fide member of this family,
and what you own will basically
belong to Arnaldo too.
That's where we'll have
a problem, Congressman.
I'm selfish. What's mine is mine.
That's why Arnaldo…
belongs only to me.
Right, hon?
[suspenseful music playing]
[Emilia] I'm having a migraine, Papa.
-A severe one.
-[Julio mutters indistinctly]
[tense music playing]
[exhales]
Ivy, before I do forget,
kudos to you
for agreeing to that prenup,
which really surprised me.
I didn't expect you to just
agree to it just like that.
And, Arnaldo, if you're looking
for confirmation of true love,
what your wife-to-be here did
was clearly a statement of true love.
[Emilia] Mm-hmm.
That's because I really love Arnaldo.
Oh, and not to pressure the two of you…
I would like to have grandchildren
very, very soon.
-[forced chuckle]
-[Julio] Because…
I'd like to still be able to guide
and teach the future
Ardientes of this family
before I…
disappear into oblivion.
Don't say such morbid things, Papa.
Don't be like that.
And besides, it's too early.
Ivy wouldn't want
to ruin her figure, right?
[chuckles]
It's not about my figure, Emilia.
I don't mind it. It's just that…
I was thinking that after the wedding,
we should prioritize
securing Arnaldo's victory
in the elections.
I think that's more urgent, right?
Now you're talking like a true Ardiente.
[chuckles]
And you've got me thinking, Ivy.
Maybe in the next elections,
you should run for office.
You should go for Congress!
As for me, I can step down
and just run for mayor.
Of course, Arnaldo can run
for reelection as governor.
That way, we'll have
full control over Ardiente.
[Arnaldo] Brilliant idea, Grandpa.
Of course, I always have brilliant ideas.
He's right.
I can just switch political positions
-Wow. Great idea.
-with Ivy, then with Grandpa.
Yes.
Hold on. What about Emilia?
Won't she be running
for a position like before?
Oh, Mama?
Well, I'm sure every grandmother
is excited to take care
of her grandchildren.
[laughs]
[Julio] That's right. That's true.
I'm sorry.
Hon, you're so mean.
A former governor turned babysitter?
[Julio] Hey, don't take that so lightly.
That's another royal title for her.
-That's right.
-Granny Lia.
It sounds like "Princess Leia."
-[glass thuds]
Congressman, I don't think
it's a good idea
to leave her jobless.
Well, she can work for my company instead.
Don't worry, Emilia,
I'll be a kind boss. Trust me.
[fake chuckle] No, thank you, Ivy.
I still have other things
to keep me occupied.
Really? Like what?
You wouldn't want to know.
It involves violence.
Excuse me.
[tense music playing]
Oh, well. She got mad again.
I guess I should go talk
to my future mother-in-law.
-[chuckles]
-Excuse me.
[Arnaldo] Go.
[Julio] Ah…
So, now you're drinking all by yourself?
No. I just tasted the wine.
Poor Emilia. I know you're jealous
because you won't be running
for any office.
I'm sorry if I'm slowly
stealing your place here
at the mansion, and in Poblacion Ardiente.
Sorry.
Me? Threatened by you taking my place?
[scoffs]
That will never happen, Ivy.
Remember, you're just a wife-to-be.
I'm the mother.
And that will never, ever change.
So, that means I will still be
the queen of Ardiente.
[chuckles]
I never really planned to steal
whatever place you thought
you had, Emilia.
But if you're going
to sabotage my wedding,
I'm telling you…
[suspenseful music playing]
I'm so scared.
You should be.
Hmm.
Hey, hon. Where's Mama?
Like I told you, she's sulking again.
What? Sulking? Who, me? Of course not.
Oh, you guys. You know,
I just got a bit emotional
because my son is about
to get married soon.
And I just realized something.
[sighs] Finally, Arnaldo,
you've found a woman who loves you,
and is ready to die for you.
And because of that, Ivy,
[sighs]
I'm going to throw you
a bridal shower party!
Just to show you how much I appreciate
all your efforts for Arnaldo.
I promise I'll make you happy!
Party! Party!
I'm looking forward to it.
A bridal shower?
-Yeah.
-[Ivy] Exciting.
-Mm-hmm.
-Thank you.
You're so sweet, Emilia.
I am.
-[Julio] So nice of you.
-Hon…
It's okay.
I'm sure Emilia wouldn't hurt me
or have me killed.
I mean, I'm confident
she wants us to get married.
Right, Emilia?
Of course! In fact, I'm so excited!
Right, Auntie?
I can tell.
[Emilia] Yeah.
[tense music playing]
[Marlon] Double-check the particulars.
Our expenses might have been doubling.
-Okay, sir.
-Thanks.
Batch, Arnaldo and Ivy's wedding
will generate enormous publicity.
We might lose if they garner
sympathy from the people.
We'll have to act on their wedding day.
Let's gather more people.
We have to expand our network,
starting with the teachers.
You're right, Batch.
We can start with the teachers.
[Arnaldo] Here you go, Grandpa.
Thank you, grandson.
Thanks for supporting me and Ivy today.
-It means a lot to me.
-[glasses clink]
For you, son, I'll do anything.
Which reminds me.
That's why I prepared a surprise
for you later on.
To celebrate your last time being single,
I'm throwing you a stag party
on the same day as Ivy's bridal shower.
Hey, Papa, I heard you talking
about a stag party.
Am I invited?
Of course not, Raul.
Knowing you, if you were invited,
you'd just steal whichever woman
I prepared for my grandson.
I'd feel bad for Emilia.
[Raul] Well, then,
you go have fun, son.
Papa, thank you so much
for devoting time to my son.
Anytime. For him.
By the way, Emilia mentioned
something about you
paying off Jaguar's henchman.
And that Jaguar found out.
I bet he's mad, Papa.
And that he's out for revenge.
What if he sends more than
just a few ants next time?
Right?
He might send the big guns.
You should be careful.
[tense music playing]
Such arrogance.
I don't like this, Emilia.
I've repeatedly warned you.
Your actions will only
get you into trouble!
Well, Auntie, I'd rather die than see Ivy
steal everything I own.
And asking or paying someone
to do it for me
is not working anymore,
so I'd rather do it myself.
That way, I'll take her life
with my own, two hands--
Then you better do
it successfully, Emilia!
Not only will Ivy hit you again,
but Arnaldo and Julio might even kill you.
I'm not afraid of Papa
and Arnaldo anymore, Auntie.
Because I have someone on my side
who is more than willing to make me,
not just a queen, but a king.
[suspenseful music playing]
[cell phone ringing]
Emilia.
[in distorted voice] I'm sick
and tired of your voice.
I want to see your beauty.
Then I called at the right time
because I'll be needing you tonight.
What for?
I'm throwing a bridal shower
for my future daughter-in-law.
Maybe you can let me borrow
some of your macho men
to entertain my daughter-in-law,
Ivy Aguas.
What if I go there
and entertain them myself?
Including your future daughter-in-law.
She might end up marrying me instead.
Are you trying to make me jealous?
Well, I can't blame you
because, first of all,
I've heard that Miss Aguas is beautiful.
And I'm handsome, so why not?
You're annoying, Jaguar.
You know, you really do remind me
of my husband.
Never mind, don't come here.
Wow. You really do like to sulk, Emilia.
Don't worry. All the wounds
caused by your husband
will eventually heal.
I'll heal them with my kisses.
[chuckles]
Well, I'll really know that you're sincere
if you send some of your men over tonight.
[tense music playing]
-[Diego] Come and eat.
-[Camia] Thanks for your time.
-Good afternoon.
-Here's the food.
There you go.
-This is Ms. Loring's specialty.
-[Pandoy] Yes, it is!
-So delicious.
-I got it from you.
[laughter]
[Loring] Please sit down.
-[Camia] Have a seat.
-Uh, good afternoon to you all.
Thank you very much for coming here.
What's the agenda of this meeting?
Uh, we believe we need teachers
like you for a fair election.
I used to be a teacher too,
and I also served as a poll worker.
I know how important your role is
in guarding the votes of the people.
[Diego] That's why we thought
of establishing an alliance
of teachers for fair elections.
Let's stop the cheating.
We want to protect you
from bribery, harassment,
and intimidation.
Thank you, sir.
At least now, we are assured
that somebody will protect us
in the coming elections.
Right, everyone?
-That's right.
And you can trust that we will protect you
as long as we help each other
strive for change.
[in unison] For a new Ardiente!
Sir, if I may.
We have a teaching drive
in Barangay Siete.
Maybe you'd like to come?
I hope you can help us out.
-[Marlon] Go, Batch.
-Oh. Of course.
We'll bring more aid
for the kids there too.
You're really impressive, sir.
You really are bringing great change.
This is for our beloved
Poblacion Ardiente.
We'll all come together
for a new Ardiente.
Diego for a new Ardiente!
-Diego!
-Everyone, for a new Ardiente!
-For a new Ardiente!
-[all chanting] Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
[man 4] Looks like we're going
to be strippers tonight.
[laughter]
Dude, it's just one night.
Let's just humor our boss.
He'll be paying us well.
I agree. Dude, show us some of your moves.
[chuckles]
I wish we were going
to Arnaldo's stag party.
Our boss would send girls over, for sure.
-[man 5] Yeah.
-[man 4] But instead,
we're going to a bridal shower.
[village chairman] Everyone!
The man we're waiting for has arrived!
-[chanting] Diego!
-[chairman] Diego Torillo!
[kids chanting] Diego Torillo!
Good afternoon, everyone!
Thank you for accepting our invitation.
Helping every village in Ardiente
is part of our program.
So, kids, are you ready for today's games?
[kids] Yes!
-Let's go!
-[kids shouting]
[feel-good music playing]
[no audible dialogue]
[heartwarming music playing]
[in unison] Thank you, Governor Diego!
-[Diego] Auntie.
-[glass shatters]
[Camia] We're going to cook--
-Ow!
-[glass shard clinks]
[Diego] What happened?
You've got a cut.
No, it's nothing.
-I'll just let it bleed--
-Where's your handkerchief?
We need to cover this.
Where's your handkerchief?
Just hold it.
Give me your hand.
Are you okay? Does it hurt?
Remember when I also covered
your wound with a handkerchief?
[soft music playing]
Thank you.
Let's go.
Come on.
You go ahead. I'll just clean this up.
-Thanks again.
-[glass shards clink]
-Chairman?
-Don't leave just yet.
Our village prepared
a little party to thank you.
Uh…
Friends!
They prepared a party for us.
-Wow!
Sure thing, Chairman. We'll join you.
-Thank you, Chairman.
-Let's go!
Okay.
-[Loring talking indistinctly]
-[laughter]
Congressman, I hope Arnaldo's
stag party will be wholesome.
Oh, I promise you, Ivy.
No fooling around for him.
Now, for me, that's another story.
-Ma.
-I know!
Arnaldo, relax. I'll take care of Ivy.
She's going to be okay. Let's go?
Come on.
-Let's go.
-[Ivy] Behave.
[Arnaldo] Of course. Always.
Chairman, thank you very much
for warmly welcoming us here.
I'll make sure
that if I become the governor
of this province,
this place will become
prosperous and thriving.
We'd just like to ask you a favor.
If we ever find ourselves in need of aid
from the citizens of Ardiente,
we hope we can count on your village.
You can count on us, Mr. Torillo.
Thank you, Chairman.
Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's dig in.
Come on! Let's eat, friends!
-[Marlon] Let's go, Batch!
-[Diego] Auntie, eat up.
-Is it good?
-So good.
[indistinct chatter]
-[Diego] It's all meat dishes!
-Pork belly.
[woman] It's yummy!
-There's a lot of food.
-[Marlon] So delicious.
It's so good!
You puked a lot that night!
-Excuse me! Excuse me.
-We weren't able to find you.
Can I have your attention, please?
-[Arnaldo] Guys, listen up.
-Excuse me.
First and foremost, I would like to say
thank you very much to each and every one
for coming on such short notice.
Thank you very much.
Congressman, we'll make sure
that this will be a memorable
night for Arnaldo, of course!
-Okay! I'll be expecting that.
-That's good to hear.
And on that note,
I'd like to propose a toast.
For Arnaldo! For his marriage,
for his success. Viva Ardiente!
[in unison] Viva Ardiente!
[tense music playing]
Hey! We all wore white
because I thought
the theme was "all white."
I'm sorry, Ivy.
I completely forgot all about
that and ended up wearing red.
I'm sorry. I'll make it up to you.
Just look at what I prepared for you.
Let's welcome my future daughter-in-law,
-Ms. Ivy Aguas, our bride-to-be!
-[applause]
We're going to have fun tonight!
A really fun, fun night!
Shall we?
Let's go?
[tense music playing]
[Emilia] Ivy, come! Look!
We have our own bartender!
And then, I got the whole place for you!
Isn't it great? Hey, friends! How are you?
Get some alcohol, okay?
Get loaded tonight! It's on me!
The booze is on me!
Hi.
Friends!
What are you doing there?
Get some drinks and load up!
Ivy, what are you doing there?
Join me here.
[tense music playing]
Oh, Ivy. You look so bored!
We should have fun, right?
Hmm? Right?
So, is this part of your plan, Emilia?
Okay. Let's have fun!
-[water splashing]
-[yelps]
[upbeat music playing]
[exhales]
[laughing]
[laughs]
Are you okay, Emilia?
I'm okay! How about you, Ivy?
Are you okay? You look a little cold.
I'm more than okay.
I can keep up with any of your games.
How about you? Are you ready
for what I'm about to do?
[giggles]
Let's have some fun! Let's go get a drink.
[upbeat music playing]
-Oh!
-There we go!
-There you have it, dude!
-One more! One more!
-One more!
-[man 7] Here it is, bro!
-[all shouting]
[Julio] Should I join you, guys?
-Last one.
-[Julio] I'm just here to watch.
-[Arnaldo] Shot! Shot! Shot!
-[man 7] This one too.
[all] Oh!
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[man 7] One more! One more!
[men shouting]
-[man 7] One more!
-[Arnaldo] Shot! Shot! Shot!
-Shot! Cheers!
-[men] Cheers!
[man 7] One more!
[man whooping] There you go!
[Arnaldo] Ah! It's so good!
[laughing]
[man whooping] There you go!
-Ah!
-[man 7] This is great!
[Arnaldo] Oh, man. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
[instrumental music playing]
[exhales sharply]
Oh, my goodness, Emilia! Ivy!
My goodness!
You two should fix yourselves.
Why did you suddenly jump in the pool?!
You're not even dressed for it!
-Thanks, Mamita.
-Well, Auntie,
that's just how
my daughter-in-law and I play.
-Right, Ivy? [gasps]
-You're so silly, Emilia! Sorry.
-Not again.
-[Claire] Oh, you guys!
Sorry.
Come on. Get up.
[whooping]
[exhales]
[Claire] Can I get that, please?
Emilia.
-Thank you.
-Wear this robe. Ivy.
Thanks, Mamita.
Well, girls!
Since we're all wet, let's have fun!
We need something to warm us up! Boys!
[upbeat party music playing]
[sinister music playing]
[instrumental music playing]
[Ivy] Thank goodness, it's over.
Ivy, have some.
-For me?
-Yeah.
Oh, thank you, Emilia. But I'm good.
Come on.
Don't be such a party pooper.
Have a drink.
Well, I promised Arnaldo
I wouldn't get drunk tonight.
Wow! Ivy, I made this
especially for you. I insist.
Emilia, I'm getting married soon.
And I don't want your son and I to fight
just because I got drunk.
I'm just trying to be a good
girlfriend, I mean, fiancée.
What?
-[all] Shot! Shot! Shot!
-[indistinct chatter]
[man 7] Three!
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[indistinct shouting]
[whooping, shouting]
Yeah!
That's some tolerance you got there, bro.
Looks like Miss Aguas is in for it
once you let loose on your honeymoon.
-[whooping, laughter]
-Ha!
Ha! Ha!
-Are you insulting Ivy?!
-No, man.
-What?
-Hey, bro. Calm down.
It's all about fun tonight.
No fighting, okay? Chill a bit.
Let's just drink.
[man 7] Why don't we show him
our surprise?
-[man 8] Okay. Okay.
-[man 7] Come on.
[Arnaldo] What surprise? Will I like this?
You bet, bro. Trust me.
-[Arnaldo] All right.
-Here it is.
Over here. Sit here, Mayor.
Just relax, Mayor. Sit here.
[Arnaldo] This better not be a prank.
No. Why would we do that?
Just sit here. There you go.
[laughing]
[man 8] Best man, you blindfold him.
Relax, Mayor. Relax.
What is this? If this is
just some dumb trick--
[man 8] Chill out. You'll see. Game!
[tense music playing]
[men whooping]
[Arnaldo] I'm nervous.
What are we going to do?
-Oh, goodness!
-[man 8] Way to go, Congressman!
[man 7] Awesome choice, bro!
You got good taste in chicks.
Very nice choice!
-[man 8] Here she comes!
-[whooping]
[man 8] All right, it's Mayor's turn!
[laughing]
Hey, I still have meetings tomorrow!
[man 8] This is great!
[suspenseful music playing]
[man whooping]
-Whoa!
-There!
-[man whistles]
-[man 7] I think he's in love.
-[man 8] Are you okay, Mayor?
-[man 7] He's in love.
-Arnaldo, are you okay?
-Can you keep up, Mayor?
-He's in love, bro. In love!
[Julio] Mayor.
-[man 8] Success!
-[men shouting]
-[man 6] It's a success!
-[man 7] Cheers to the mayor!
-[Julio] That's it, my boy!
-[man 8] Oh, man!
-[man 7] Yeah, man!
-[Julio] Hey, hey, hey!
Arnaldo, where are you going?
-He's going to take her home.
-I'm fine. I'm fine.
[indistinct shouting]
Follow him. He's had too much to drink.
Come on! This is really good.
Go, just have it.
[Emilia] No, I don't want
to drink tonight.
-I'm gonna pass.
-See?
That makes two of us.
-So, you mixed it yourself?
-Yeah.
Well, if neither of us wants to drink it,
why don't you try it, Mamita?
-Me?
-Yeah. Try it.
-No. I already have a drink.
-It's okay. Taste it.
Emilia made it herself.
-[fake chuckle]
-No, thank you.
Aww. Mamita doesn't want to try it either.
I really don't want
to drink tonight, though.
Arnaldo and I can't fight again.
So, you have it. Thank you.
No, no, no. I'm fine.
-Thank you.
-[Ivy] Come on, don't let it go to waste.
I'll even help you. Come on.
I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine.
No, come on, just a sip.
-[Claire] Oh my god.
-[Ivy] Taste it, just a little.
Say, "Ah."
-Come on, just a little.
-[muffled exclaim]
[suspenseful music playing]
[muffled exclaim]
[gagging]
[suspenseful music playing]
Why?
Emilia!
[suspenseful music playing]
[retching]
[water running]
Emilia! Emilia!
So, how does it feel
to fall into your own trap?
I don't know what you're saying!
Oh please, Emilia.
Are you actually trying to play dumb?
[coughing]
Aunt Claire! [crying]
[Claire] Emilia! Emilia!
What's happening to you?!
That woman poisoned me!
-What?!
-"Poisoned"?
This actually contained poison?
What poison did you switch with mine?
-[retching]
-Oops.
I didn't switch anything. I'm innocent.
How the hell did you get that?!
[suspenseful music playing]
I don't like this, Emilia.
Your actions will only
get you into trouble!
Well, Auntie, I'd rather die
than see Ivy steal everything I own.
[suspenseful music intensifies]
It's simple, really.
I'm Ivy Aguas, remember?
You poisoned me! [retching]
You poisoned yourself.
Emilia, I read that this particular poison
is one of the worst.
Your throat will constrict.
So tight that you won't
be able to breathe!
-[wheezing]
-[Ivy] Just like that!
And then, it will make
your whole body shake!
It will make your body shake so badly
that you'll feel like passing out.
But it will--
[Claire] Oh, gosh! You have to throw up.
You have to throw up, Emilia!
Spit out the poison!
Do it! Hurry!
-Keep trying!
-[Emilia retching]
Put your finger in your mouth!
That's it! Keep trying!
[laughing]
That's it! Come on!
Do it! Come on! Keep going!
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[retching]
[Arnaldo] You're very beautiful, Ivy.
I just want to talk to you.
[woman, crying]
This wasn't part of the deal.
[Arnaldo] Why are you giving me
a hard time?
Mayor, I'm not Ivy.
What are you talking about?!
-Reporting for duty, Mayor.
-Madrigal. Long time no see.
Just like old times, Mayor.
The only difference is that
I work for Jaguar now.
He wants me to tell you
that your days are numbered.
Is this the last time we'll see
each other before your wedding?
[Ivy] Maybe, maybe not. Thank you, Diego.
[Diego] Take good care of yourself,
okay? Be careful.
[theme music playing]